Use your heart and truly see
The truth is right before your eyes
Hey you good or bad, true or false
Step out of this smoky haze in your soul
Bring all your courage along
Maybe then you can save the world
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Mojo Spy
MagiEye
Everyone, MagiEye Corp. is now having its grand opening!
I'm telling you—the most fun, most exciting game in the world, MagiEye Angel
has landed in Tuna Town!
Too hot to handle! Players, don't miss it
This once-in-a-lifetime chance
Come join now!
【MagiEye Angel: A Citywide Hit】
Dear viewers, this truly is a miracle
A brand-new computer game has this much pulling power
Angel! Look, the angel is here!
Though celebrities are easily adored
Being called an angel really embarrasses me
Miss MU, Miss MU!
Sell it to me! I want it! Give it now!
What game is that? That's amazing.
Really? No way?
It's not just some fake ad, right?
Hey, where's Jingjing?
Wow, that's crazy! You actually knocked Miss MU down!
Meow! One, two, three, four!
Two, two, three, four!
Three, two, three, four!
Exercising every day is important, you know~
What are you doing?
My Miss MU!
One, two, three, four!
Two, two, three, four!
Three, two, three, four!
You're not listening at all!
Don't block people from watching TV!
The little girl picking mushrooms
Carries a big bamboo basket on her back
You gotta stay energetic every day————
Uncle
Hurry up and think of something
Make this little hyperactive girl
calm down!
Got it!
Move, move! I need to get out!
What? Sold out?
We waited in line all day!
You're telling me it's sold out?!
The last one was sold to that guy.
That's him.
You... What are you going to do?
Stay back!
[Forget violence and blood for now. Let's enjoy the beautiful flowers.]
I'm back.
Jingjing.
This is a gift for you.
What is it?
Something really fun.
But you have to promise me.
You'll play with it nicely.
The most important thing is
to stay quiet.
Okay.
Got it?
No problem.
What a beautiful round plate.
Awesome!
Can I eat this?
This is the latest MagiEye Angel.
Great!
You stop right there.
You're not allowed to play.
Why?
This is what I bought for Jingjing.
Then where's mine?
Go play with it.
Thanks, Uncle.
I'm your own nephew!
I'm so miserable.
I live in a
family without love.
Uncle.
Yes, I'm Jimmy Chen.
Hello.
Let's play this game together.
No.
Why?
Just got a call.
Someone mysteriously got sick.
We need to investigate the cause.
Let's go. Time to work.
But Uncle, I—
What? Already don't want to be a detective?
Uh, fine.
The owner of this residence...
Just now, while working on the computer
he fainted out of nowhere
Is he awake now?
No
He's been unconscious since being rushed to the hospital
His breathing is weak
The doctors say they can't find any illness
Strange
What could be wrong?
Indeed, strange
We can only try to find clues in his room
What's this?
What? Did you find something?
Look — everyone's playing this newest game
Stay focused! This is no time for playing games!
Hey
Little gadget freak
What? Someone else passed out at the computer?
That's five in a row
who've collapsed at their computers
Could it be an infectious disease?
Everyone's playing MagiEye Angel
I wanna play too
Me too
Everyone who passed out
Everyone's playing MagiEye Angel.
This game!
I want to play too!
Jingjing!
You've been playing all day.
You should take a break.
Yeah, yeah, it's my turn now!
No!
I haven't had enough yet!
Go away!
Don't bother me!
Hmph, what a grouch.
Jingjing, what's wrong?
I'm fine. I'm great.
This game is so awesome!
Thanks, Uncle!
Jingjing, you...
You've been playing too long.
Do you feel any discomfort?
[untranslated] 没事 我好得很
Don't worry about me.
Any progress?
Reporting, Mr. K!
We're now extracting the vitality of all MagiEye Angel players, one by one.
It won't be long.
The Heart of Vitality crystal bottle will be filled smoothly.
Awesome!
Dear Mr. K
You're so brilliant, sir.
Looks like we'll be done with our mission soon.
Long live the great Illumin-Eye!
Right
Hurray!
Ah, how could this be?
Report, Lord K.
The Vitality Source supply is already running low.
What should we do?
You good-for-nothing!
You just said it was going well!
What's going on here?
All players, open fire!
We've almost sucked it all dry.
I don't care.
Crank it up!
1. I need to complete the firepower collection at once.
2. Report, Mr. K, sir!
3. Found a player with an extremely strong Vitality Source.
4. Let me see.
5. So it's her.
6. Get in here!
7. Concentrate all your firepower on her!
8. Drain her vitality until there's not a drop left.
9. Report, Mr. K, sir!
10. A massive energy stream is flowing in from far away, endlessly.
11. Then let's unleash our full vitality.
12. Let's end this game as quickly as possible.
13. Long live The Illumin-Eye!
14. Hail! Hail!
15. [End Credit Song]
16. Look at tomorrow
17. Waving to me from the horizon
18. Each day goes from sunrise to sunset
19. Spin into time and imagine more
20. In life, I look forward
21. To every second, every moment
22. Bright eyes are shining
23. A smile that meets the sun
24. Breaking through the bridge
25. At the silent crossroads